[Destiny and Saving] [EP11]
Miss Ye,
why did you get so nervous
when I mentioned the word scratch?
Are you telling me
that if you can't get into Ling Shenxing's bed,
you're just a useless pawn of the Ye family?
Think about it.
You're not even as good as Cardamom.
She knows how to help the Ye family,
but you...
You are a loser!
They asked me to persuade you
to listen to the Ye Family.
So,
you are also here to force me?
I dare not.
But Miss,
if you keep doing this,
not only will you be looked down upon in the Ling Family,
but I will also suffer with you.
Following a useless master like you,
I can only be slapped by others.
How dare you!
Miss,
don't blame me for being rude.
If you can't come up with a solution,
I'll tell my master
to take you back.
You also want to force me?
I trusted you so much.
Tell me,
what else can I do?
What else can I do?
Enough!
This stops here!
Bad news!
Madam!
Second Concubine!
The
elderly gentleman's boat sank!
There are no remains left.
Ah!
Madam!
Mom!
Someone help!
Come here!
I'm coming!
You're on your period and not feeling well.
Go back and rest.
My lady,
if you're not feeling well,
you should go back and rest.
Women are inherently yin,
and you're on your period.
What if
you offend your uncle's spirit?
What should we do then?
What?
Lady Shen came to the mourning hall
during her period?
Menstruation
is the most unclean.
How dare you come to your uncle's funeral?
If it delays his reincarnation,
you
will be to blame.
You filthy woman,
how dare you
come to the wake during your period?
You wicked woman,
trying to stain his path to the afterlife?
Are you hoping he'll never find peace?
Who isn't stained?
Menstruation is a natural physiological process,
a part of the body's metabolism.
How did it become impure?
This is scientific common sense,
not some omen of disaster.
You...
I'll hit...
Women spend half their lives
women suffer from menstruation.
Without it,
there would be no offspring, no continuation of the human race.
If this is considered dirty,
then the mothers who gave birth to us
are all sources of filth.
The world would rot into mud,
and we wouldn't be here to judge it.
As for whether the elder uncle's path is clean,
it depends on whether he has lived a just and honorable life.
If he is,
he won't be afraid of being slandered.
You...
You dare to talk back to me for her.
You dare to question the rules of our ancestors.
Do you still have me in your eyes?
Do you still have our ancestors in your eyes?
Go get thirty strokes of family discipline.
Then come back.
Kneel for ten hours
in front of your uncle's coffin.
Kneeling for a long time can compress the femoral artery,
causing poor blood circulation in the legs
and muscle hypoxia.
You've been kneeling since dawn
without eating anything.
It's easy to cause low blood sugar.
If you keep going like this,
you'll faint.
I mixed this with your favorite liquor
and added half a cup of honey water,
reducing the alcohol content to the lowest.
It can promote blood circulation
and relieve numbness.
The glucose in it
can also increase blood sugar.
It's much more effective than ordinary sugar water.
This pastry
is made with millet flour,
easy to digest
and can slow down the drop in blood sugar.
I'll keep an eye on the door for you.
Eat something to tide you over.
No one will notice.
In Ling residence,
there's a rule against eating in the mourning hall.
You're already exhausted from dealing with your uncle's affairs.
If you get sick,
it will be taken advantage of by those with ulterior motives.
Drink it quickly.
I just went to check.
The Old Madam
is resting in Shoukang Garden.
Fuyuan is guarding the door.
No one will find out.
And
you're kneeling here because of me.
If you don't drink,
I'll feel bad.
It has nothing to do with you.
She's just showing her authority.
In the Ling Family,
she is an insurmountable mountain.
I...
From now on,
thank you.
You not only helped me deal with her,
but also spoke up for women.
You are my nominal wife.
It's my duty to protect you.
Ling Shenxing's uncle never showed up before.
But after I delivered a gift
from Chu Nanfeng to the old marshal,
[he just disappeared,]
[leaving no trace.]
[Could it be]
[that there's a clue in this study?]
[Oh no, someone's coming.]
Isn't Ling Shenxing out today?
Why is he back so suddenly?
I was wondering about the smell of medicine.
So the young madam of the Ling residence
is a thief in my study.
What's going on?
Don't move.
I'll do it.
I'm not mistaken.
It's gallop rhythm.
It's done.
Ah.
Do you
take medicine for a long time?
Tell me.
Yes.
Take it out.
This is the sleeping pill I've been taking.
The medicine has a strong bitter taste,
which is ephedrine.
The medicine was replaced.
It contains a large amount of ephedrine.
If your heart is normal,
overdose of ephedrine
will induce arrhythmia
and lead to heart failure.
What does that mean?
In short,
someone wants to kill you.